Ghost Meets Gal!
Wow, I can't believe we got the same room.
Yes, I'm so relieved!
This has gotta be fate.
Fate...
Heh, it's a bit embarrassing,
but you're right.
I'm so hyped!
So, Dra-Em is like, really dry, which makes
taking care of my skin such a pain.
Really? But your skin is so shiny, Santhi.
Sun protection is a must for me.
Sure, come in.
Alestiel
Dorm Leader
Good evening.
I'm Alestiel, your dorm leader.
Alestiel
Dorm Leader
Don't disappear, Lubnacchi.
There, there.
I'm sorry for dropping in so suddenly.
I'm just going around
explaining the rules.
Is that so? Appreciate it.
I see, so you're the rumored honor student.
Huh?!
Santhi, you're an honor student?
Yeah, like, apparently.
An honor student? So she's exceptional?
She's going to leave me behind
and debut at top speed!
Her popularity will skyrocket.
She'll be a huge hit!
A top idol.
She'll probably forget about me.
Santhi, congratulations!
Uh, who were you again?
I'll end up dying alone...
Oh, I forgot I was a Ghost!
Each floor takes out its trash together.
Gotcha~
Looking down, sighing,
hiding my true feelings
Every time i step forward,
even if i'm trembling,
I can't lie to my desire of change!
It's surely a distant dream right now,
but i want to chase it together!
Even if our futures are different colors,
Let's paint them with the same dream.
Because you are the one who gives me courage!